Hi, and this lesson I will show you how to create an account for a JGPTIM or OpenAI.
Uh, first with the JGPTIM.com, you can open a link from the resources for this lesson or you can just find it in Google.
Uh, after it you can click login or sign up this page boss, so it doesn't matter what you click.
If you already have an account, please login and skip this lesson, but if you don't,
you can create your account using Google provider if you have just your Google email.
Um, I use this way, it's my preferable way.
You can also use Microsoft account, you can use Apple, phone, or just email others.
After the type, email others you will need to edit, password, and then you can create an account.
Um, OpenAI also might need to verify your email or phone number, but it takes only a few minutes
you will get a letter on your email or SMS just to confirm a temporary code.
Okay, after you'll log it in or create an account, you will see the JGPTIM interface,
you just list on the left and at the bottom you will see an input where you can find
and type a messages.
So now account is ready and see you in the next lesson where I will see you
also magic how to work with Charles and other functionalities.